And so
Basically, the idea of projects being bets is
It's kind of a bit like this
So, I don't know if you're familiar with Damon Runyon. He's the guy who wrote the stories that became Guys and Dolls, the musical
And
This is a quote from him. I long ago came to the conclusion that all life is six to five against. So I'm not a betting man, so I had to look up what six to five against meant
And a lot of behavior that we see around projects
Is connected with the fact that
We don't really want to acknowledge that. We don't really want to kind of pretend that there's a possibility to not pretend. We want to pretend there's no possibility of the project failing. We want to rather
Imagine that the project is going to always succeed.